莫妮卡 这真是史上最棒的感恩节大餐 太好吃了
Monica,that was the best Thanksgiving dinner ever.It was so good.
你把我们撑死了
I think you killed us.
我连一口都吃不下了
I couldn't possibly eat another bite.
我要吃点甜的
I need something sweet.
有人想看电视吗？ 好啊
Does anyone want to watch TV?
莫妮卡，你的遥控器按不动
Monica,your remote doesn't work.
你得把它拿起来对准
You have to lift it and point.
算了
Oh,forget it.
你们知道吗？ 我们应该来玩感恩告白游戏
Let's play that game where everyone says one thing they're thankful for.
我要说 感谢今年的秋天这么美
I am thankful for this beautiful fall we've been having.
说得真好
Very nice.
那天我在等公车
The other day,I was at the bus stop...
突然吹来一阵秋风 把一个女生的裙子吹了起来
...and this lovely fall breeze came and blew this chick's skirt up.
对了，我还要感谢丁字裤
Which reminds me,I'm also thankful for thongs.
本集播出：“感恩大回顾”
The One with the Thanksgiving Flashbacks
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
与其说它是内裤 不如说是一种伟大工程
It's not so much an underpant as a feat of engineering.
料子那么少，效果却那么大
It's amazing...how much they can do with so little material.
它还会戏弄你 有穿吗？没穿吗？
And they play with your mind. Is it there? Is it not there?
你知道你还在唠叨吗？
Are you aware that you're still talking?
有没有人要感谢 丁字裤以外的东西？
Is anyone thankful for anything else besides a thong?
我不知道要比较感谢离婚 还是被赶出来
I don't know. Am I more thankful for my divorce or my eviction?
我还以为你会没得谢
And I didn't think you'd be able to come up with anything.
抱歉，这是最惨的一次感恩节
I'm sorry. This is the worst Thanksgiving ever.
不不不，我才是悲惨感恩节之王
No No No I am the king of bad Thanksgivings.
你不能以失败的婚姻为理由抢了我的宝座
You can't swoop in with your bad marriage and take that away from me.
你又要说你爸妈离婚的事了？
You're not going to tell about your parents' divorce again,are you?
别这样嘛，我想听
Come on! I want to hear it.
没有钱德扫兴就不算感恩节了
It wouldn't be Thanksgiving without Chandler bumming us out.
这跟游行一样是一项传统
It's a tradition,like the parade.
如果游行也包括同性恋和抛妻弃子的话
If the parade decided it was gay and abandoned its family.
“1978年感恩节”
钱德，爸爸和我要离婚 并不代表我们不爱你
Now,Chandler,dear...just because we're getting a divorce doesn't mean we don't love you.
只是代表他上床的对象是男仆 不是我
It just means...he would rather sleep with the houseboy than with me.
钱德先生还要火鸡吗？
More turkey,Mr. Chandler?
你把那家伙的口音 说得越来越重
Every time you tell that story,that guy's accent gets thicker and thicker.
他们还在一起吗？
So are he and your dad still together?
没有，他们同居之后 男仆自己也有了男仆
No. After they got their own place,the houseboy got his own houseboy.
你应该听听他的口音
Should have heard his accent.
你说得对，你的更惨 你是悲惨感恩节之王
You're right,yours is worse. You're the king of bad Thanksgivings.
不一定，我有一次更惨
I've got one that's worse.
惨过“钱德先生还要火鸡”吗？
Really? Worse than,"More turkey,Mr. Chandler?"
小少爷跟仆人有仇吗？ 对，我的更惨
Did the little rich boy have a problem with the butler?Yes,mine's worse!
“1862年感恩节”
还要绷带！还要绷带
More bandages!More bandages!
再给我一些绷带 这个人快…
Please,can I get some more bandages in here?This man is
哦，不
Oh no
今生的才算，菲比
In this life,Phoebe.
今生是吧，那钱德的比较惨
Oh,this life. Oh,okay.No,Chandler's is worse.
记得前世的事一定很酷 我都没有前世的记忆
It must be cool remembering stuff like that.I don't have any past-life memories.
当然没有，你是新生命
Of course,you don't,sweetie. You're brand-new.
我知道莫妮卡最惨的感恩节
I know Monica's worst Thanksgiving.
那个就别提了 说嘛
Let's not tell this story.Come on
我知道，就是莫妮卡的火鸡 卡在乔伊头上那次
I know!It's the one where Joey got Monica's turkey stuck on his head.
什么？乔伊头上卡了只火鸡？
What？Joey got a turkey stuck on his head?
其实不是那样 其实就是那样
It's not like it sounds.It's exactly like it sounds
“1992年感恩节”
菲比？
Phoebe？
乔伊？怎么了？
Joey？What's going on?
你看
Look
我的天哪 我知道，它卡住了
Oh,my God!I know!It's stuck!
小心台阶 它怎么会跑到你头上？
Step.How did it get on?
是我套上去想吓钱德
I put it on to scare Chandler.
天哪，莫妮卡一定会气死
Oh,my God! Monica's going to totally freak out!
那就赶快帮我拿下来 而且这里面好臭
Help me get it off!Plus,it smells really bad in here.
当然很臭 你的头塞在动物尸体的屁股里
Of course it smells bad. You have your head up a dead animal's ass.
是莫妮卡
Monica
你替火鸡涂…我的天哪
Did you get the turkey?Oh,my God!
那是谁？ 乔伊啦
Who is that?It's Joey.
你在干什么？你是在搞笑吗？
What-what are you doing？Is this supposed to be funny?
不是搞笑，是吓人
It's not supposed to be funny. It's supposed to be scary.
马上给我拿掉
Get that off now!
拿不掉，卡住了
I can't. It's stuck!
我不管，我爸妈的二十个客人 可不能就着你的头吃
Well I don't care！That-that turkey has to feed 20 people at my parent's house and they're not going to eat it off your head!
先别急，大家一起想办法
Hold on.Let's just all think.
我知道了，菲比，你拉 我尽量把腿撑开
I got it!Phoebe，You pull.I'll spread the legs as wide as I can.
乔伊，现在不要闹 对不起
Joey，Now is not the time.Sorry
好，数到三…一，二，三
Count to three. One...two...three!
成功了！我吓到你了
It worked! I scared you! I knew it!
大哥，我在这里
I'm over here,big guy.
我知道
Yeah,you are!
我吓到你了
I scared you!
你看起来真的很白痴
You did look like an idiot.
白痴的不只是我
I wasn't the only one who looked like an idiot.
罗斯有一次想说冬南瓜 结果讲成南冬瓜
Remember when Ross tried to say "butternut squash"...and it came out,"squatternut bosh"?
的确一样白痴
Yeah,that's the same.
那就是我最惨的感恩节
That's it. That's my worst Thanksgiving.
等等，瑞秋说的不可能是那次 她根本不知道那件事
Oh wait！That can't be the one Rachel's talking about.She didn't even know that happened.
所以是哪一次？ 哪一次？
So,which one was it?
我真的不想提这件事
I really don't want to tell this story.
讲嘛，重温悲惨的回忆 是感恩节的精神
Reliving pain and getting depressed is what Thanksgiving's all about.
至少我觉得是 还有印第安人也是
For me,anyway.And,of course,the lndians.
最不希望我提的绝对是你
Of all people,you do not want me to tell this story.
什么意思？
What is that supposed to mean?
“1987年感恩节” 莫妮卡，应该是瑞秋来了
-Monica,I think Rachel's here!
我来开
-I'll get it!
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving!
我不快乐，奇普和我分手了
Not for me.Chip and I broke up.
为什么？怎么了？
Why?What happened?
你知道的 我爸妈要出门 奇普要来…
My parents are out of town,and Chip was going to come over.
对，你要给他你的花芯
And you were going to give him...your "flower."
莫妮卡，你能不能直接说做爱 你那样讲让我浑身发毛
Monica,can you just call it sex?It really creeps me out when you call it that.
还有，在做的时候 男人的那里不叫他的温柔
And by the way...while we're at it,a guy's thing is not called his "tenderness."
相信我
Believe me.
瑞秋
Rachel
感恩节快乐 你也是
Happy Thanksgiving.You too sweetheart
天哪
Oh my！
各位，这是钱德 我的室友兼我们乐团的主唱
Everyone...this is Chandler.My roommate and lead singer of our band.
罗斯
Ross
这是莫妮卡 我是罗斯的妹妹
This is Monica.I'm Ross' little sister.
好
Okay
欢迎你来，有很多吃的 希望你饿了
I'm so glad you could come.We've got plenty of food,so I hope you're hungry.
妈，钱德痛恨感恩节 他不吃感恩节食物
Chandler hates Thanksgiving and doesn't eat any Thanksgiving food.
哦，很高兴你带他来
I'm so glad you brought him here.
钱德 我可以帮你煮起司通心面
Chandler I can make you some macaroni and cheese for dinner.
只要当年的清教徒没吃我就吃
As long as the Pilgrims didn't eat it.
讨厌
Damn it!
瑞秋，我去上大学不在家 你会不会觉得怪怪的？
So uh，Rach？Does it feel weird around here now?You know,since I've been away at college?
那倒不会 那就好
Not really.That's cool.
那你…
So did…
她就是你那些歌的女主角瑞秋 对
So that's Rachel,the girl you've been writing all those songs about?
你可能得修改那句 “我的离去令她浑身不对劲”
Might want to rethink the lyrics to "She Feels Weird Since I've Been Gone."
奇普居然为了那个花痴南西 而甩了我
I cannot believe Chip dumped me for that slut Nancy Branson!
我再也不跟他约会了 他再怎么求我也没用
I am never going out with him again. I don't care how much he begs.
他有了南西，应该不会求你了
His begging days are over,now that he's with Nancy Branson.
你知道吗？我受够高中男生了 他们全是些又笨又呆的小毛头
I've just had it with high-school boys.They're just silly.They're just silly,stupid boys.
我要开始跟男人交往
I'll start dating men.
茱蒂，对不起 我找不到你和杰克要的碗
I'm sorry,Judy.I couldn't find that bowl you and Jack were looking for.
叫爸爸妈妈，傻瓜
Call them Mom and Dad,you loser.
莫妮卡
Monica
钱德
Chandler
起司通心面好吃吗？
Did you like the macaroni and cheese?
很好吃，你应该去当厨师
It was great. You should be a chef.
好啊
Okay
你猜怎样？ 南西很花痴的传闻都是假的
Guess what.All this stuff about Nancy being a slut was all a rumor.
所以奇普甩了她 他今天晚上想来找我
Chip dumped her,and he wants to come over to my house!
太棒了 就是啊
-That is so great! -I know.
天哪，要是你和奇普晚上做了 你一定要把细节都告诉我
Oh,gosh. Listen,if you and Chip do it tonight...promise me you'll tell me everything.
那当然，其实也没什么 我们应该算是做过一次
Totally. It's not that big a deal. We already kind of did it once.
我知道，但这回你一定能确定 我知道
But now you'll definitely know whether or not you did it.I know.
奇普还保证 这次会持续一整首歌的长度
And Chip promised that this time it'd last at least for an entire song.
我晚上打算约瑞秋出去 弹我们上周写的那首歌给她听
I'm thinking of asking Rachel out tonight...maybe playing her that song we wrote last week.
“忧愁的背包”？ 对
"Emotional Knapsack"?  Yes
漂亮
Right on!
不过不要拖太久
But don't take long.
我们今晚还要去试用假身份证 对吧，克里夫艾维瑞兹？
We're testing our fake lD's tonight.Right,Clifford Alvarez?
听着，罗兰陈
Listen,Roland Cheng...
如果一切顺利 我们搞不好不会回来
...if things go well,I may be out with her all night.
兄弟，别丢下我
Dude,don't do that to me.
没关系，你可以留下来 我爸妈不会介意
It's cool,you can stay here. My parents won't mind.
不是，我不想整晚 跟你的胖妹妹在一起
It's not that. I just don't want to be stuck here with your fat sister.
莫妮卡，把这些派吃完吧 冰箱塞不下了
Why don't you finish off these pies?I don't have any more room in the fridge.
不了，谢谢
No,thank you.
茱蒂，你成功了 她终于吃不下了
Judy,you did it.She's finally full!
我说你胖？我完全不记得
I called you fat? I don't even remember that.
或许唱那首“忧愁的背包” 可以让你想起来
-Maybe it'd jog your memory...if you guys played a little bit of "Emotional Knapsack."
对不起，真的 我那时候很愚蠢
I'm so sorry. I really am.I was an idiot back then.
我还在威猛乐队的演唱会上 冲上台大叫
I rushed the stage at a Wham concert,for crying out loud!
你居然说她胖
I can't believe you called her fat.
你居然让乔治·迈克尔（威猛乐队成员）赏你耳光
I can't believe you let George Michael slap you.
真的很抱歉，我太差劲了 真是对不起
I am really sorry.That is terrible. I'm so sorry.
其实我说的不是那次感恩节
That's not the Thanksgiving I was talking about.
就是 不是，我说的是…
Yes,it was.No,it wasn't.it was actually
感恩节结束，准备过圣诞节吧 谁要去买圣诞树？
Thanksgiving's over. Let's get ready for Christmas.Who wants to go get a Christmas tree？
我有最可爱的圣诞节故事
I have the cutest Christmas story.
我们想听莫妮卡的感恩节故事
We want to hear Monica's story.
我的故事里有小矮人断成两截 不过随便
Mine had a dwarf that got broke in half,but,you know,whatever.
“1988年感恩节” 瑞秋，你妈说你又转系了
So Rachel，your mom tells me you changed your major again?
没办法 心理系的楼旁边很难停车
I had to.There was never any parking by the psychology building.
瑞秋
Rachel
你的新鼻子真漂亮 杰克
Love your new nose!Jack
威尔森医生是个艺术家
Dr. Wolfson's an artist.
他帮我点掉一堆痣 你要看吗？
He removed my mole cluster.Want to see?
我去开 不，让我去
I'll get it.No! Please,let me.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
你的发型变了好多
Your hair sure is different.
我们刚才还在讲 我们以前的造型真的好蠢
We were just talking about that.We can't believe how stupid we used to look.
莫妮卡呢？ 在楼上
Where's Monica?She's upstairs.
莫妮卡，快下来，人都到齐了
Monica，Come down,everyone's here!
罗斯，瑞秋 和那个痛恨感恩节的男生
Ross,Rachel...and the boy who hates Thanksgiving.
钱德 我的天哪
Chandler.Oh,my God!
怎么了？我的衣服有脏东西吗
What's the matter?Is there something on my dress?
你变了好多好漂亮
You look so different.
那件裙子，那个身材
Terrific.That dress,that body....
喂 抱歉
-Dude! -Sorry.
对，莫妮卡瘦了，太好了
Yes,she's thin. It's wonderful.
但我们比较关心罗斯的新女友 拜托老妈…
But we really want to hear...about Ross' new girlfriend.Oh，mom
好吧，她叫卡萝 她很漂亮，很聪明
Okay，Her name is Carol.She's really pretty and smart.
她是长曲棍球和高尔夫球校队成员 很厉害吧？
She's on the lacrosse team and the golf team.Can you believe it?
她两个校队都打
She plays for both teams.
钱德，那就晚餐见啰
So I guess I'll see you at dinner.
喂 抱歉
-Dude! -Sorry.
天哪，真是酷毙了 你完全报了一箭之仇
Oh,my God!That was so awesome.You got him back for calling you fat.
他的口水流了满地 感觉一定很过瘾
He was drooling all over you.That must have felt so great.
一点也不过瘾 什么？
lt didn't.What？
没错，我很漂亮，感觉很好 心脏的毛病也没了
Yeah,I mean,I look great.I feel great,and my heart's not in trouble anymore.
但我还是觉得没报到仇
I just don't feel like I got him back.
我想狠狠地羞辱他
I just want to humiliate him.
我想让他光着身体 再指着他大笑
I want him to be naked,and I want to point at him and laugh.
好，搞不好可以
That,we may be able to do.
怎么做？
How?
男人要做爱之前都会脱光衣服
Guys tend to get naked before they're going to have sex.
什么？我这么努力瘦这么多 可不是为了把花芯给他那种人
What?I didn't work this hard and lose weight just so I could give my flower to someone like him.
好，第一，你再那样讲 保证没有人会要
First of all,if you keep calling it that,no one will take it.
第二，又不是要你来真的 只是要你误导他
And then second of all,you're not going to have sex with him.You'll just make him think that you are.
也对
Yes
等他脱光了 我就把他赶出去锁上门
I'll throw him out in the yard,lock the door...
让所有的邻居耻笑他
...and all our neighbors will just humiliate him!
那你就绝对报了仇
You'll definitely get him back.
我要怎么误导他？
How do I make him think I want to have sex?
我知道了 假装什么都能让你兴奋
Here's what you do.Just act like everything around you turns you on.
什么意思？ 就是什么都能挑动你
What do you mean?Anything can be sexy.
像…像这条擦碗巾
Like this dish towel.
它的触感好舒服
This feels so good against my cheek.
如果我热了就可以拿它来吸汗
And if I get a little hot,I can just dab myself with it.
或是把它放在腿边 边跟他说话边玩弄
Or I can bring it down to my side and run it through my fingers...while I talk to him.
这个我会 很好
I can do that.Good,good,good.
他来了
Get busy. He's coming.
你好
Hey,what's up?
莫妮卡，你能不能帮我煮 去年那种通心面
Could you make me some of that righteous mac and cheese like last year?
没问题
I'd love to.
我好喜欢起司通心面
I love macaroni and cheese.
我好喜欢这个盒子的触感
I love the way this box feels against my cheek.
好
Okay
我好喜欢红萝卜
And I love carrots.
有时我喜欢把它们这样夹着
Sometimes I like to put them between my fingers.
然后放在腿边跟你说话
Like this.And hold them down here while I talk to you.
觉得很热的时候，我喜欢…
And,you know,if I get really hot...
拿起这把刀 把冰凉的刀身靠在…
I like to pick up this knife.And I put the cool steel...against
身上
...my body.
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
我很好，只是…
I'm fine. it's just that…
什么状况？
What do we got here
20岁男性，右脚拇趾被切到
Twenty-year-old male.He's got a severed toe on his right foot.
别撞到他的脚好吗？
Could you please not do that feet first?
你明知他是拇趾被切到 你刚才也说了
You know where his injury is. Severed toe,you just said it!
这里写说刀子刺穿鞋子
It says the knife went through your shoe.
那当然，他穿的是草鞋
Of course it did.They're made of wicker!
断指带来了吗？ 有，在这里冰着
Did you bring the toe?-Oh yes！I have it right here on ice.
“冰上拇指秀” 麦迪逊花园广场即将演出
Toes on Ice,coming soon to Madison Square Garden.
省点力气吧
Save your strength,man.
放心，我们会把它缝…
Don't worry,son. We'll just reattach it and then....
怎么了？
What is it?
你带了一块红萝卜来
You brought a carrot.
什么？
What？
这不是你的脚趾 这是一小块很冰的红萝卜
This isn't your toe. This is a small,very cold piece of carrot.
你带红萝卜来？
You brought a carrot?
天哪，我的厨房里有一截断趾
Oh,my God!There's a toe in my kitchen.
对不起，我马上回去拿
I'm sorry! I'll go get it!
来不及了，我们只能直接缝合
All we can do now is sew up the wound.
我的脚趾没了？我需要我的脚趾头
Without my toe? I need my toe!
等一下，我很快 爸，让我开你的保时捷
I can go really fast! Dad,give me the keys to your Porsche.
我才不会上当
I'm not falling for that one.
这就是我断趾的原因？ 因为我说你胖？
That's why I lost my toe? Because I called you fat?
我不是故意的，那是意外
I didn't mean to cut it off. It was an accident.
我就因为这样被叫了一整年的 跛脚趾头先生？
That's why for an entire year people called me Sir Limps-a-lot?
对不起嘛 又不是一整根脚趾头
I'm sorry.It wasn't your whole toe.
我少了趾尖，趾尖是最棒的部分
Yeah,well,I miss the tip.It's the best part.
趾尖有指甲
It has the nail.
钱德
Chandler
跛脚趾头先生 那是我想出来的
Sir Limps-a-lot.I came up with that.
你好无聊
You're a dork.
我真不敢相信
-I can't believe this.
钱德，我都道歉了
-I said I was sorry.
道歉也换不回 我那思乡情切的小趾尖
"Sorry" doesn't bring back the piggy that cried all the way home.
我就知道今天会发生这种事 我恨感恩节和这一天的一切
It figures that something like this would happen today.I hate this stupid day and everything about it!
回见 等等，过来
I'll see you later.Wait.Come here.
有什么我能做的吗？任何事
Is there anything I can do? Anything?
有，让我静一静
Just leave me alone for a little while.
我是鸭子呱呱呱 一天到晚都快乐
I'm a duck. I go quack-quack.I'm happy all the time.
别试了 等等
Nice try.Wait,wait,wait.
莫妮卡… 你看
Look,Monica
没有用的
This is not going to work.
接下来绝对有用
I bet this will work.
你真绝，我爱你
You're so great.I love you.
什么？
What？
没事，我说“你真绝” 然后就没说话了
Nothing. I said you're so great,and then I just stopped talking
你说你爱我，我真不敢相信
You said you loved me. I can't believe this!
我没有
No,I didn't!
你有 我没有
Yes,you did!No,I didn't!
你爱我 我没有
You love me!No,I don't!
别再说了
Stop it,stop it,stop it!
“1915年感恩节”
纱布！这里需要纱布
Gauze!Gauze!I need to get some gauze in here!
请再给我一些纱…
Can I please get some more gauze?
真是越来越荒谬了
This is getting ridiculous.